Records of the Athletics Department RG.41
New York University Archives
- RG 41.4: Football, 1889-1967
  - Football Team Programs, Pamphlets, and Roster, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - "Football Facts" and Team Roster, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - NYU vs. Columbia, Fordham, Rutgers, 1922-1964 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Football Team Rosters and Press Releases, 1933-1939 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Football Team Narratives, Rosters, and "Football Facts", 1930-1939 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Football Team Statistics, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Football Team Roster and Press Release and "Football Facts", 1933 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Football Team Statistics, Rosters, and "Football Facts", 1934 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Football Clippings, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Football Team Rosters and Statistics, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Football Team Information and Rosters, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - "Football Facts", 1937 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Football Team Statistics, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Football Team Statistics, Rosters, Press Releases, and "Football Facts", 1938 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Football Team Statistics and "Football Facts", 1939 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Football Team Rosters, Statistics, Press Releases, and "Football Facts", 1940 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Football Team Clippings, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Freshmen Football Statistics and Roster, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - 1911 Football Schedule (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Football Schedule and Trinity vs. NYU Game Program, 1912 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Trinity College vs. NYU Game Program, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Rensselaer Pol. Institute vs. NYU Program, 1914 24 Oct (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Football Game Programs, 1915 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Football Game Programs, 1916 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Football Game Programs, 1917 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Trinity vs. NYU Program, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Football Schedule, 1920 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Football Schedule and Programs, 1922 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Football Game Programs, 1924 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - NYU vs. Niagra, 1925 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Football Game Programs, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Football Game Programs, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Football Programs, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Football Programs, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Football Game Programs, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Football Game Programs, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Football Game Programs, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Football Game Programs, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Football Game Programs, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Football Schedule, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Football Game Programs, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Football Game Programs, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Varsity Football Statistics, 1945-1946 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Football Game Programs, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Football Statistics and Game Programs, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Football Game Programs, 1947-1948 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Football Game Programs, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Football Game Programs, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Football Game Programs, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Football Game Programs, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Agnone, John J. Player Biography, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Barnes, Hester Player Biography, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Bernstein, Charles Player Biography, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Bonacorsa, Joe Player Biography, 1958-1964 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Boroff, Paul E. Player Biography, 1942 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Bunyan, John T. Player Biography, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Burney, Bill Player Biography, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Campanis, Alexander Player Biography, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Carapella, Al Player Biography, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Cestary, Roy Player Biography, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Cherico, Ross Player Biography, 1944-1945 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Collins, Leo V. Player Biography, 1927-1930 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Comerford, Charles A. Player Biography, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Concannon, Ernie Player Biography, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Connolly, Robert V. Player Biography, 1936-1945 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Connor, John J. (Dutch) Player Biography, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Consagra, Joseph Player Biography, 1939-1968 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Devore, Hugh Player Biography, 1950-1953 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Dickson, George Player Biography, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - DiGaspari, Vince Player Biography, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Dintman, Herbert Player Biography, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Dowd, Dan Player Biography, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Dunney, Howard E. Player Biography, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Feibish, Bernard Player Biography, 1946-1947 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Furiel, Ralph Player Biography, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Gersh, Edward Player Biography, 1943-1945 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Gladchuck, Chet Player Biography, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Jackson, John Player Biography, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Healey, Joseph Player Biography, 1956-1978 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Lassman, Alfred Player Biography, 1930-1933 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Lassman, Alfred Clippings, 1928-1930 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Intercollegiate Football 1869-1934 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Football Policy Discontinuation, 1941-1942 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Football Policy Discontinuation, 1941-1942 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Student Petition on Discontinuation of Football Program, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Football Clippings, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Varsity Football Statistics and Clippings, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Football Resinstated Clippings, 1944 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Varsity Football Statistics and Press Release, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Football Clippings, 1944 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Football Clippings and Press Information, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Football Clippings, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Football Clippings, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Football Clippings, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Football Clippings, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Football Clippings, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Football Clippings, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Football Clippings, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Football Statistics and Press Information, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Football Clippings, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Club Football Press Information, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Club Football Statistics and Press Information, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Football Policy/Discontinuation, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Football Clippings, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Club Football Statistics and Press Information, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Club Football Clippings, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Club Football Clippings, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Club Football Statistics and Press Information, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Club Football Statistics and Press Information, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Club Football Clippings, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Football Discontinuation, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- RG 41.5: Gymnastics, 1898-1906
  History of Gymnastics at NYU
  Gymnastics makes a brief appearance in the history of athletics at NYU. It was first practiced in 1894 after the addition of the University Heights campus in the Bronx. In March of 1897 the Athletic Association held the first dual gymnastic meet for prizes. There, NYU defeated Lehigh University. Two years later NYU hosted its first intercollegiate gymnastics event with 19 other colleges. Events included the horizontal bar, tumbling, club swinging, fence vaulting, rings, parallel bars, high jump, and the side horse. World War I interfered with the burgeoning team's growth, and the team was disbanded in 1919.
  This series is comprised of New York University gymnastics meet programs and tickets ranging from 1898 to 1906.
  - Gymnastics Programs & Tickets, 1898 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Gymnastics Programs, 1899 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Gymnastics Meet Flyer, Undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Gymnastics Programs, 1900 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Gymnastics Program, 1902 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Gymnastics Programs, 1903 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Gymnastics Programs, 1904 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Gymnastics Program, 1905 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- RG 41.6: Track and Field, 1899-2007
  History of Track and Field at NYU
  The earliest mention of New York University's track and field team is in the University Heights 1896 Violet yearbook. Since then, NYU has aided in the training of many track and field Olympians. The earliest track meets were held outside at Ohio Field on the University Heights campus, which was constructed in 1900. In 1912, the New York University Track Association held its first annual indoor meet at the 22nd Regiment Armory. In 1971 coach Joe Healey was named the United States Track Coaches Association Coach of the Year.
  Today men's and women's track and field teams continue to compete at the varsity level in the University Athletic Association Conference.
  The Track and Field Series contains track event programs, statistics, and newspaper clippings as well as player biographies. Track sports began at NYU in 1895, and this series has records dating back to 1899 and continuing somewhat sporadically through 2007.
  Men's and women's track and field results for 2003-2014 are located in Archives H. Men's and women's cross country results for 2000-2014 are located in Archives H.
  - Track and Field Program, 1899 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Track and Field Program, 1901 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Track and Field Program, 1903 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Track and Field Program, 1909 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Track and Field Programs, 1912 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Track and Field Program, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Track and Field Program, 1933 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Track and Field Schedule, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Track and Field Programs, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Track and Field Statistics and Clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Cross Country, Indoor, & Outdoor Track, 1945-1946 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Cross Country, Indoor, & Outdoor Track and Field, 1946-1947 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Track and Field Schedule, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Cross Country, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Castro, Frank Biography, 1923-July-12 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Dyce, Byron Biography, 1966-1969 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Edwards, Phil Biography, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Ellis, Larry Biography, 1951-1952 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Engel, Martin Biography, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Healey, Joseph F. Biography, 1957-1969 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Hooten, Denise Biography, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Marshall, Shelly Biography, 1971-December-2 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Mondschein, Irving Biography, 1948-1949 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Pearman, Reginald Biography, 1947-1948 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Sieja, Stanley Biography, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Schoolman, Irving Biography, 1956-1961 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Toussaint, Cheryl Biography, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Weber, Jake Biography, 1946-1948 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Wedderburn, Jim Biography, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- RG 41.7: Athletics Department administrative files, 1945-1980
  This series contains a correspondence file of Director of Athletics Dan Quilty. Quilty served in this position from 1972-1996. The file represents several years of communication with Vice President for Student Affairs Jane Maggin.
  - Athletic Department Administrative Files, 1976-1980 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- RG 41.8: Coles Sports Center, 1981-2010
  History of Coles Sports Center
  The Coles Sports Center, located at 181 Mercer Street, was opened in 1981 and named after NYU alumnus and benefactor Jerome S. Coles. The new facilities provided the University, which had recently returned entirely to its downtown campus, with a location for sporting events, team practices, health and wellness activities, and community recreation. The Coles Sports Center served as the home for NYU's NCAA Division III teams and also hosted a number of events including NCAA Men's and Women's National and Regional Championships in basketball and fencing as well as international wrestling and fencing competitions.
  In 2014, NYU announced plans to demolish Coles and build a new facility in its place.
  This series is comprised of Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information Booklets and Program Guides ranging from 1981 to 2010 and arranged chronologically.
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1983-1984 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Coles Sports & Recreation Center Information/Procedures Booklet, 1995-2010 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1982-1983 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1992-1994 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1998-1999 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Coles Program Guide, 1999-2003 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Coles Program Guide, 2004-2005 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Coles Program Guide, 2005-2006 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Coles Program Guide, 2006-2007 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Coles Program Guide, 2007-2008 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Coles Program Guide, 2008-2009 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- RG 41.10: NYU Olympic Athletes
  History of Olympic Athletes at NYU
  NYU athletes have been competing in the Olympics since 1904. Between that year and 1988, 19 athletes from NYU have won a total of 28 medals.
  Fencing and track have generated the most Olympians from NYU. In 1988 an exhibition was created to highlight the successes of NYU's Olympic athletes.
  This series is comprised of materials relating to the NYU Olympic athletes from 1904-1988, including rosters and biographies of these athletes as well as material from a 1988 exhibition on NYU athletes who have competed in the Olympics.
  - NYU Olympians: Exhibit Correspondence and Captions, 1988-1990 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, Cliff Bertrand, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - NYU Olympic Exhibit, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - NYU Olympian Booklet (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Penn State at the Olympics (A model booklet), 1988 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Chronology, no date (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - NYU Panam Games Athletics, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Statistics of Participants, undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Team Member Listing/Addresses, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Listed by Sport/Event, undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Info on NYU Olympians, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - 1904 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - 1912 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - 1920 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - 1924 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - 1928 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - 1932 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - 1934 Track Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - 1936 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - 1940 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - 1948 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - 1952 Team (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - 1956 Team (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - 1960 Team, undated (Box 46, File 24)
  - 1964 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - 1968 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - 1972 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - 1976 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - 1980 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - 1984 Team, undated (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - 1988 Team (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Addresses for NYU Olympians, undated (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Millrose Games, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Apostol, Paul, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Armitage, Norman, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Baird, George, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Ballinger, Ed, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Becker, Benjamin, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Bertrand, Cliff, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Byrnes, Joseph, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Calarese, Wladimiro, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Cann, Howard, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Carnevale, Bernard, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Castello, Hugo, undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Castro, Frank, undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Checkes, Jeffrey, undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Cohen, Herbert, undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Conwell, Edward, undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Corbitt, Ted, undated (Box 47, File 16)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Cumiskey, Frank, undated (Box 47, File 17)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Cunningham, Glenn, undated (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Dasaro, Mike, undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Davis, Martin, undated (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: de Caprilles, Jose, undated (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: de Capriles Miguel, undated (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Denman, Elliot, undated (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Dickson, Gordon, undated (Box 47, File 24)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Dow, Robert, undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Dyce, Byron, undated (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Edwards, Philip (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Ellis, Larry, undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Engel, Martin, undated (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Feurbach, Leon, undated (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Frontera, Jim, undated (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Furth, Sol, undated (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Giolito, Silvio, undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Glazer, Gene, undated (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Griffin, Jack, undated (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Gubner, Gary, undated (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Guira, John, undated (Box 47, Folder data_value_missing_445b108d567aca6227ac2a32691e04b7)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Hammon, Graeme, undated (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Healey, Joseph, undated (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Heiss, Carol, undated (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Hurme, Risto, undated (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Jones, Gilbert, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Jones, Samuel, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Kaplan, Steve, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Keane, Jack, undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Lang, Martin, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Lapp, Bernice, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Lewis, Norman, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Lindstrom, Lisa, undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Lofton, Michael, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Lumpp, Ray, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: MacDonald, Bruce, undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Macknowski, Steve, undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Mason, George, undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Master, Edith, undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: McGary, Ethel, undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: McKenzie, Gordon, undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: McSheehy, Jones, undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Mondschein, Irving, undated (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Moore, Roy, undated (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Mormando, Steve, undated (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Novick, Dean, undated (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Ornstein, Charles, undated (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Park, Dong Keun, undated (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Pearman, Reginald, undated (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Pechinsky, Sally, undated (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Peterson, Gus, undated (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Pinkasov, Seymon, undated (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Poprata, Dolph, undated (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Prokop, Austin, undated (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Rossini, Lou, undated (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Scandurra, Aldo, undated (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Schoolman, Irving, undated (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Scrobe, Edward, undated (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Sieja, Stanley, unknown (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Spitz, George, undated (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Stone, Donna, undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Toussant, Cheryl, undated (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Voliva, Richard, undated (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Von Elling, Emil, undated (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Walker, Leroy, undated (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Walker, Stuart, undated (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Walz, Allen, undated (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Washburn, Mary, undated (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Weber, Jake, undated (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Wedderburn, Jimmy, undated (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Westbrook, Peter, undated (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: White, Ruth, undated (Box 48, Folder 47)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Wieselgren, Hans, undated (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Witzk, Herman, undated (Box 48, Folder 49)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Woodruff, John, undated (Box 48, Folder 50)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Zaremba, Peter, undated (Box 48, Folder 51)
  - NYU Olympic Athletes: Zuaro, Vincent, undated (Box 48, Folder 52)
- RG 41.11: Tennis, 1919-1976
  History of Tennis at NYU
  Men's tennis gained varsity status in 1907 and the first squad consisted only of four players. From the 1919 to 1927 seasons the men competed without a coach. During the 1930s the men's team consistently made the New York State Intercollegiate Championships. Men's tennis is strictly a spring sport.
  Women's tennis started at NYU in the late 1920s. The team played only in the spring until 1973, when they added fall competition.
  Men's and women's tennis teams continue to compete at the Division III level.